Do you want to make it real,
like we're in a relationship?
Oh my, does Nero have telepathic skills
that he can read my mind?
Does he want to kiss me?
You're holding my hand so tightly.
You can let go now.
No one is...
looking.
I'm sure you're not stupid.
Do you really think
that Nero will just have
a new girlfriend overnight?
I'm not one to make silly assumptions
when it comes to other people.
The fact is, Nero and I are over.
So, he can do whatever he wants.
If there's something that bothers me,
that's you.
I thought you'd be interested
to know the real score
between Nero and Florence.
And I thought you're interested to know
that all of this is just an act.
Who is she in your lives?
She's our cook.
Are you telling me all this
because you want me to break them apart?
This is a dangerous playground
that you're in.
And it looks like you and Nero
are about to be involved
in a seriously complicated situation.
Are there any problems with my ideas?
Are there things you don't like,
or do you want to add something?
It seems that's not what we're expecting
to talk about in this meeting.
Huh? Why?
What should we talk about?
About the Grand GU Ball.
Yes.
Grand GU Ball?
Weren't you informed, Florence?
It's the most important event here in GU.
So as our student representative,
I think it's a good idea
that we should all brainstorm
for this upcoming event.
I'm sorry, Florence,
but the Grand GU Ball is not just a party.
Yes, and this year is very important.
That's because the Com Arts are
the designated host of this grand event.
Maybe I'm also pressured
with being the student representative.
Think about it,
I thought of a lot of ideas and projects
to make our university better
but then, all they want to talk about
is just one thing,
the Grand GU Ball.
What hurts the most,
is I don't understand anything
about what they're talking about.
If there's something
you don't understand in this world,
don't hesitate to ask me.
That's the least I can do.
Thank you.
It's still early.
Let's eat first.
Soup? 450 pesos per bowl?
What's that?
Do the ingredients have gold dust?
Why is it so expensive?
I'm hungry okay?
Stop overreacting.
I'll be the one who will pay for it.
Overreacting, Nero? Me?
They're overpriced.
No! This is a luxury, Nero.
And besides, there are a lot of
cheap eateries in the area
that are delicious.
So, if you want to eat, go ahead.
I will not eat here.
Whatever is left, I'll donate to charity.
Okay fine,
where is this place
accepted by your moral standards?
Are you smiling?
Mister, one more isaw, betamax,
and chicken ass.
Hey, what's with you?
You became serious all of a sudden
when I saw you smiling.
Too bad, whatever you do,
I already saw you smiling.
I can't unsee that anymore.
Come on, smile one more time.
Smile... Smile.
You're so grouchy.
You know, that smile of yours,
Antonia must see that whenever she sees you.
Because I'm sure
that if she sees you smiling,
she'll reconcile with you,
because her heart will melt
if she sees you smiling.
Smile... Come on, smile.
Just one more smile. Smile.
Come on, smile now.
Just one.
Hurry. Don't be too stingy with your smiles.
Just one smile.
You're holding back your smile.
You know what?
Now that I made you smile,
let's go back to talking about cheap food.
Did you think
I've already forgotten about it?
You know, I can't really accept
where you took me earlier.
Imagine, just soup...
that kind of soup, the serving is so small.
I think one cup of rice
is much bigger than that.
How much was that? 350 or 450 pesos?
It was so expensive.
Here, the cheapest price is 7 pesos,
while in that restaurant,
I think the lowest price
is the appetizer at 350 pesos.
Here, look at this at 20 pesos,
you'll have all the meat.
It's worth it already.
You, rich people,
are so used to
that kind of luxury restaurant.
If you'll buy here
and use up all your money here...
Come hurry, smile.
She makes you hopeful.
She makes you brave.
Brave enough that you can be happy.
And she makes you understand
that in order to be happy,
you have to embrace it,
grab it, and choose it.
And when the opportunity comes,
you shouldn't be scared.
Smile.
Come on, smile now. Just one.
Hurry. Don't be too stingy with your smiles.
Are you smiling?
Mister, one more isaw,
betamax, and chicken ass.
He's more cowboy than me.
So, his favorite fruit is rambutan.
And it seems that his favorite food
is grilled stuff at Hepa Lane.
Good job, Florencia.
You're slowly solving Nero's mysterious side.
In fairness...
he's fun to be with.
His future girlfriend will be lucky.
I am my own woman,
I can handle everything
that will be thrown at me.
But, you're right.
You're something else.
You have a strong influence on me.
- Who?
- Oh my God!
Stop sneaking in!
You always enter a frame without a set-up.
What's that?
Do you want to find out?
What's with this place?
Just wait.
You even have lights.
Come here.
Hold that... and spread it out there.
Here.
Why do you have a comforter?
Well, just play along. Spread it out.
That's it.
Lie down.
Wait a second.
Let me just fix this.
There.
Are you ready?
- What?
- Are you ready?
- I'll count to three...
One, two, three.
- Hey, you pervert!
- Ouch, what's that?
- You pervert!
- Ouch!
You're planning something else, aren't you?
- What do you mean I'm planning?
- You have an evil plan, right?
- No!
- Let me go!
- Florence, wait! Calm down, okay?
- Just calm down.
- What? What are you doing?
- Here.
- What are you getting from your bag?
- You're going to kill me, right?
- I'm not planning anything.
Wait! I don't have any evil plans.
Here it is.
Here.
What's that?
Here, try it.
Can you be killed by this?
Look up there.
What's this?
What can I see here?
- Saturn? Jupiter? Mars?
- There is it.
There... Let me.
Orionids meteor shower.
Those are remnants of Halley's Comet.
Imagine, the last time we saw Halley's Comet
was in 1986.
But even now, we can still feel it.
I hope I have that kind of impact
on the person I love.
Even if I'm no longer around,
she can still remember the beautiful memories
that I left for her.
There, look at it.
It's over there.
Hurry.
Is it beautiful?
It's beautiful.
Yes, it's beautiful.
Go ahead and look if it's beautiful.
Okay.
It's really beautiful.
Yes...
it's very beautiful.
Let's share.
Okay, you can use the other side.
Your forehead is too big.
- Wait, let's adjust it.
- Did I offend you or not?
Not really. But just for tonight...
- Tomorrow is...
- Well, it's beautiful.
Come on, let's look again.
Coffee. So you won't be sleepy
in your class later.
Thank you, Owen.
You're really an angel
just when I need extra strength for today.
Why did you stay up late last night?
How did you know I stayed up late last night?
It's just a guess because
I saw you yawning now.
Come, why don't you ride with me to school?
Let's go, Florence.
Bro, I'll take Florence to school.
I will.
I'm the boyfriend.
Do you mean fake boyfriend?
Besides, I asked her first.
So what?
Basic rule of firsts, Nero.
I don't care.
Remember I told you,
the first chance you get, break it off.
I understand you're trying
to protect Florence,
but this is getting ridiculous.
Florence and I have an agreement.
And she agreed to help me,
so don't meddle anymore.
She agreed or she was forced
because she owes you something?
It doesn't matter.
I will bring her to school.
- Let's go, Florence.
- No, she's going with me.
Stop it.
I don't need both of you.
I can go to school on my own.
Here, have some coffee...
so you will both be nervous.
Nero is so possessive, as if we're a couple.
- And Owen meanwhile is acting this way.
- What happened?
You were suspended
because of your stupid shenanigan
during the Agora day.
You had the guts to do something foolish,
but you didn't do it correctly.
Dad, let me explain.
Dad!
- Hey, excuse me.
- Dad...
You shouldn't hurt her.
Florence, stay out of this.
No, Camille. You shouldn't let someone
hurt you like that.
He's my father.
Still, Camille.
Even if he's your dad, he doesn't have
the right to hurt you that way.
And you... You're a father
but you act that way.
You even look educated.
Are you familiar with RA 9262
Anti Violence against Women and Children?
Hey you, don't meddle!
This is a family matter.
So, just because you're a family,
you can hurt her just like that?
Shouldn't you not hurt her instead?
Because as far as I know, if you're a father,
you should protect your child.
Don't you dare lecture me like I'm a child!
I'm sorry.
You went into beast mode immediately
when you can talk to Camille peacefully.
You're a grandson
of Don Garpidio Ferell, right?
So, don't meddle here or else...
Or else what?
I have no issues with the Ferells.
It's this woman who owes me, so don't meddle.
For your information,
the girl you're messing with
is also a Ferell.
I suggest you back off, Mr. Villarico.
Sir, please.
Let's not make decisions
that we'll regret later on.
You speak so arrogantly.
Grandfather Garp...
Yes, Grandfather.
Yes, we're with Mr. Villarico,
Camille's father.
Trouble?
Guys, are we in trouble?
Grandfather Garp is asking.
Are we, Mr. Villarico?
Let's go.
I will be okay, Florence.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I'll call you.
- Thank you.
- I'll make sure you're okay.
Huh?
What?
Who is that woman you're talking to?
Woman? What do you mean woman?
You're the only woman in my life.
That's Troy.
You're something else.
You easily get jealous.
Me? Jealous?
Please!
What does Troy need?
You know, it was so weird.
All I understood is
there was a Mr. Villarico.
And he even called me Grandfather Garp.
Maybe he's playing a prank.
Serafica, do you want to take a bath?
Excuse me?
Why would I want to bathe with you?
Please!
It's more fun to take a bath together.
Serafica...
- What?
- Here I come...
I'm coming I'm here now.
- Stop it. Someone might see us.
- Run now! Go ahead and run.
- I'll go after you.
- I don't want to run.
- No!
No... No, don't stop.
Come on.
Are you serious?
Do you really have to call
Grandfather Garp about that?
You just made the mess bigger.
Grandfather Garp is the least
of your concerns.
What were you thinking, Florence?
Why did you confront Mr. Villarico?
Because he is hurting Camille.
Do you think I'll just let it go?
What if it's you who got hurt?
Did I get hurt?
No, right?
Because we arrived, Florence.
Even if you didn't arrive,
I can protect myself.
So stop being protective, Ferell guys.
I'm not a damsel in distress that needs
a knight in shining armor
who will save me.
You know you can't do it
on your own all the time.
I agree. From now, just stick with us.
A Ferell should always be with you,
so you'll be untouchable.
Huh? What? You'll keep an eye on me?
And then, you'll interfere with my decisions
in life, right?
Thanks for your concern, but no thanks.
No!
Ouch!
Florence is so brave, isn't she?
That's what these two guys like...
Strong, independent, and annoying women.
Don Rogelio, he's here already.
Good afternoon, Sir.
Don Rogelio...
Again, I'm sorry I wasn't able
to attend our meeting.
Something happened earlier.
Camille had some trouble in school.
And to make matters worse,
I had a confrontation
with Don Ferell's grandsons.
Really?
Yes, Sir, and a...
A Ferell woman started it.
A Ferell woman?
Oh, Florence, can we talk?
It's about...
Antonia, I know about your past with Nero.
- But I hope...
- Oh, Florence, stop.
We won't be talking about Nero.
Whatever is going on between you and him,
it's really none of my concern.
We won't be talking about that?
Yes, but anyway, I just want to remind you
about our meeting later
with the student heads
about the ball.
Your department will spearhead it, right?
I hope you've already prepared a plan.
Yes, I've collected the suggestions
of my fellow Com Arts department students.
I'll be presenting our plans later.
Perfect.
Well, I'll see you around.
A Ferell woman?
Yes, Sir. There's a Ferell woman in GU.
Are you sure?
As far as I know,
Garpidio doesn't have a granddaughter.
Well, those boys claim
that she's a Ferell too.
But, it's the least of my concern.
What worries me is that,
Don Ferell might pick on us.
In the middle of our confrontation, Sir...
one of his grandsons called him.
And I'm so worried, Sir,
because the highway project that you gave me
is dealing
with one of the properties of Don Ferell.
We need to fix this.
We cannot afford another delay
in this project.
What are we going to do, Sir?
Let me handle this.
Excuse me, Don Ferell.
You have a phone call, Sir, from Don Rogelio.
Still alive, Rogelio?
I should ask you that question.
Bad weeds take a long time to die.
Let's give ourselves another ten years
and see who is the worse weed.
Alright.
So, what's with this call?
Is the world ending?
No, not yet.
But one of my men, George,
had an unfortunate encounter
with your grandchildren.
Why don't I pay you a visit,
so we can talk about this problem?
Welcome, everyone.
I'm excited about the big projects
with all student representatives.
Aira is here on behalf of Aylip,
who has always been supportive
of the grand GU Ball.
And because of the hosting disaster
of the Philosophy department,
I'm sure anything that we will do this year
will be a success.
So, let's turn it over to Florence,
the Communication Arts representative.
She and her department
are the hosts this year.
And in the history of the grand ball,
Com Arts has had
the most memorable and powerful impact.
We set the standards.
So, let's hear it from Florence.
Actually, I compiled all the suggestions
of the student leaders of my department,
each one is representing an organization
under Communication Arts.
Yes, and it was fun
because for the first time,
everyone was given a chance
to give suggestions,
and Florence listened to every one of us.
Of course.
First, someone suggested
that we do it like a Coachella music festival.
That's nice.
I've actually been to several Coachellas,
and if we can replicate the atmosphere,
that would really be amazing.
Not to mention,
singing and dancing to our favorite music.
Singing and dancing...
Okay... next suggestion.
Le Bal des Débutantes.
Someone suggested that too.
Oh! I prefer that.
Among the Ferells,
I was the one who attended
an event like that in Paris.
That's really interesting.
It's not that fun,
but the event is well-executed
and choreographed.
Next suggestion...
someone suggested that we do it
like Il Ballo del Doge.
A masquerade ball.
That one is fun.
Fun because you can hide your ugly face.
Florence, what's your decision?
Actually, the truth is,
all the suggestions are beautiful, right?
But for me, whatever this body wants,
we can go for that direction.
What I want is for our ball to
have a deeper meaning this year.
So, what do you mean by that, Florence?
The ball should be more than
our fancy dresses or big venue,
expensive food.
I want to make it a fundraising event
for the communities who are in need.
We can mount a simple ball,
but if we were to spend
a huge amount of money
because it's GU's grand ball,
I hope we don't take for granted the reality
of living hand-to-mouth,
because not everyone here in GU is well-off.
Some people work every day
so their families can eat.
So, if you're going to ask me,
I want it simple but elegant.
Fun but there's meaning
outside our university,
and we'll be able to help others.
The meeting earlier was okay, right?
- Yes.
- Hey, Florence, you're so good.
Good job.
Thank you.
That's weird.
Why?
She's an Aylip, and she's being kind to you.
It looks like you're no longer
a persona-non-grata to them.
You're done being a TWPS.
(*The Worst Person in School)
I hope so.
I don't want to be a TWPS anymore.
Florence.
Antonia.
I really like your ideas.
I just feel bad, because you're right.
We, who are born into privilege,
we tend to take for granted
the reality that exists outside of us.
It's not yet too late.
More or less,
the capitalists have ten years
to save the planet, our world,
or else, well then, we'll all die.
I equally love your sense of humor.
We should discuss the details next meeting.
I have some ideas
that we can use for the ball.
It was really nice talking to you.
I'll see you later.
Does she think you're joking?
Isn't she aware with the recent IPCC Report?
If we won't be doing anything,
earth will vanish.
Why?
I just feel guilty.
With what?
About you and Nero?
Florence, it's over between her and Nero,
and you're together now.
And it looks like she has moved on already.
Oh well, I'll just tell you
the whole story next time.
What? Which one?
Well, next time... next time.
Let's see each other later.
There's someone I want to talk to.
Bye.
Aira!
Aira...
Can we talk?
What do you need?
Are you here to gloat?
To celebrate
that Camille and I are miserable.
No.
Actually, I want to talk to you.
I want to check on you and Camille.
You guys can go ahead.
Honestly, she's having a hard time.
She got suspended,
that's why the last time I heard,
her father is fuming mad.
If you only know her father, Florence.
You won't believe what he is capable of.
No, I believe you, Aira.
Yesterday, while I'm on my way to school,
I saw Camille's father hurting her.
That's expected.
I've known for years
that Camille's dad is abusive.
He wants Camille to be always on top
that's why with just a little mistake,
my friend would be slapped.
I remember the first time I met her.
Eleventh place?
When we received the letter,
I was expecting
that at least you'd get in the top five
of those who took the exam.
Eleventh?
How come?
You didn't even make it to the top ten.
Dad?
Dad...
I'm so sorry.
You're nothing but a big disappointment.
I'm so sorry, Dad.
That was the first time I saw her.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
We've been horrible to you.
We did a lot of things
so you'll be miserable.
Even then,
no one deserves to get hurt that way.
I don't want to make excuses.
Because what we did to you was really wrong.
But maybe, I was enabling Camille...
because I know the miserable life
that she has.
I'm so sorry for that, Florence.
If only we got to know you better,
Camille and I will like you as well.
But no, we judged you.
And worst, we made you feel
that you don't belong in this world.
That's okay.
It's never too late to heal and forgive.
That's why I want to talk to you,
and I want to talk to Camille as well.
Are you sure?
Why are we here?
Why are you making me hurry?
What is this, Aira?
Is this a trap?
Did you make me come here
so she can laugh at me?
So they can gang up on me?
Camille, no.
Then, what is this for?
Is she doing a blog for bullies?
No, Camille.
This is us showing you that we understand
what you're going through now.
We want to assure you
that whatever you're going through,
we are here for you.
And if you need help,
we're ready to help you, whatever that is.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why are you so kind to me
after all that I did to you?
Because, Camille, I believe
that everyone deserves a second chance.
Except for Hitler.
But you, you deserve that.
Why are you so kind?
You're annoying.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
I'm sorry for being mean.
I'm sorry for everything.
That's okay, Camille.
Stop crying...
Don't cry anymore.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Just smile.
Cheers!
Wow, that's great.
I told you, Florence.
Start talking about the grand ball,
and the process of healing will be faster.
You're really good in exposing people.
Don't worry. You're still my bestie.
I like you both,
and I would love to be friends with you.
But in the hierarchy of friends,
Camille is still on top of my list.
Stop it.
That's where you start looking down
on others,
with that hierarchy.
- Wow, changed person.
- Yeah.
If I find out that you two are starting
to be mean and be bullies,
you'll answer to me.
- That's right.
- That's right!
True...
Okay.
I think that is your superpower, Florence.
Everybody eventually wants
to be friends with you.
Even Antonia, who is the former ex
of your boyfriend Nero.
Why?
I want to change my life.
I don't want to say bad things
about others, but...
Florence deserves to know.
Yeah.
It's not that I want to badmouth others,
but... be careful of Antonia.
Why?
Well, she's the real deal, Florence.
I mean, I admit that I'm not a good girl,
I'm an in-and-out mean girl,
but Antonia seems like
she's hiding a different persona...
and that's scarier.
She's the Queen Bee.
And do you think the queen will easily agree
that you'll get one of her belongings?
Those two were something else.
That's because they're used to talking about
a lot of nonsense.
But I don't think so, Antonia looks nice.
But Antonia seems like
she's hiding a different persona...
and that's scarier.
She's the Queen Bee.
And do you think the queen will easily agree
that you'll get one of her belongings?
Florence?
Yes?
Is there a problem?
Hurry up, Don Ferell is asking for you.
Why?
Do I look like a gossip-monger to you?
Why? What did you do this time?
Come on. You hurry up.
Leave that... Leave that!
Excuse me, Don Ferell.
Florence is here already.
Grandfather Garp?
So you're Florence Dela Cruz?
Florence, I'd like you
to meet George Villarico.
He's an associate of Don Rogelio Almero.
- And this dashing gentleman here is...
- I am Rogelio Almero.
This guy, George,
claims that you attacked him.
Is it true?
Yes, Grandfather Garp, that's true.
So it's true.
I kicked him on his...
Beep... Beep, beep...
First, why did you meddle?
He was just talking to his daughter.
And then when he asked you
to leave him alone,
you kicked him there.
That's very disrespectful, Florence.
I cannot tolerate such behavior.
Cannot be.
I'm sorry if I kicked you on the... beep.
But, Grandfather Garp,
if I need to do it again, I'll do it.
What? You'll do it again?
Why?
Because he was physically hurting his daughter.
What reached you was a fake story
that I just hurt him without a valid reason.
I was defending Camille.
And that's what my mother and father taught me,
Grandfather Garp.
If I see someone getting abused,
I need to help.
George, is this true?
Pardon me for what I did, Sir,
please let me explain.
I'm under a lot of pressure
and when I found out
that Camille has a problem in school,
I completely lost my temper.
Let's talk later.
What you did is admirable, Miss.
I commend your courage
in standing up for others.
I felt it right away
that she was Celestina,
my missing granddaughter...
Son, I think I found your daughter.
I have found Celestina.
What?
The on-and-off battle
between me and Don Rogelio
goes a long way back.
And it's not just about politics.
Don't tell me, Grandfather,
you also had a competition on love?
Yup.
Florence?
Look, I'm sorry
that we met under unfortunate circumstances.
I understand.
There's nothing to worry about.
Oh, but look, what do we have here?
Is Mr. Henry your favorite too?
Mr. Henry's chicken?
You, too?
Is that your favorite?
Actually, I didn't discover this place.
It was my daughter-in-law, Alyanna.
It was suggested to me by my friend
who owns an IT company.
He sent me a computer graphics expert.
Look.
That is the rendered picture.
That is Celestina's picture.
I have a strong hunch
that this is your missing daughter.
That's Celestina.